Boom. Nailed it.
Oh, hi.
What brings you to this part of the video?
I was hoping that I could talk to you guys through annotations, but subtitles will have to do.
Why did they take annotations away? Seems like Youtube is blowing it every day.
Anyways.
This is KJAZZ. It's the local jazz radio station out of Long Beach.
It's chill, especially on nice rainy days like this one.
I'd highly suggest that everyone learn about their local radio stations, actually.
You'll find your local conservative radio station, I'm sure.
That one is especially fascinating, the way that they signal to their religious base and choose what topics to cover.
Also it seems like every other interview they have is with someone who gets cut off mid-interview for saying something that doesn't agree with their agenda.
It's brilliant, the way they do it. They don't even say bye to the guest.
One minute they're talking and giving an answer, the next they're gone.
This cover is interesting... it pulled me in because I grew up on Indiana Jones like most 31 year olds
but is it actually good? I don't know.
But I keep paying attention to find that they've changed the words to be about today's politics!
Another strike against them, at least I know I won't get any re-listens from something that's so specific.
Would you relisten to a song that's this topical?
But alas, I'm a hater.
Anyway, you might also have a crazy liberal radio station to pair with the crazy conservative radio station.
The best I can describe it as the worst of Democracy Now! interviews... over and over.
It seems like most of the people they talk to have nothing concrete to say, instead rambling about bad energy and demonizing the conservatives.
These guys will also censor what they cover and what they won't. For example they won't let someone say that  the DNC sabotaged Sanders' campaign in favor of Hillary.
I'm rambling myself, at this point.
Ironic.
So this is the fabled 405 North. It's my least favorite freeway on Earth.
My favorite is the 13 in northern California. It's a windy thing that you can take quite fast late at night.
Deja Vu!
Sorry, wrong genre.
This tune is pretty nice, right?
I think so. But I've realized that the best way to really get through bad traffic is to sing. I don't think I'll film any of those, but it's just something I've noticed.
Singing is hard and I'm not particularly good at it.
This video goes well as a pairing with a nice Skywalker OG preroll because you're a lazy piece of shit and you're willing to pay extra to not roll them yourself.
Have they talked yet?
I was planning on not typing during the talking out of respect for the person talking...
Anyway, the world is divided. That's all I'm really saying. And it's really fun to learn about how divided it is and how they're dividing us.
That's all. Read ZeroHedge every once in a while to understand what those people think. Do the same with Vox.
Excuse me...
I should donate.
Oh I guess we're back at music again! Anyway. I might do this later with some of my favorite albums. That might be interesting to give commentary on the music itself.
I smoked more during the talking, so excuse me if I slow down.
So I'm going to be driving up to the LAX airport, more or less.
This was a surprisingly easy drive given how much it was raining. Not sure how I always dodge the traffic.
So what else is happening in the world? Have you ever felt like music stopped happening around 2001?
I have. I think it has to do with the establishment of a "Second Top 40" list that they call "Adult Alternative"
or something like that.
I heard it on NPR, it was pretty fascinating. But that's probably just because I like music (though I hope you do too if you're watching this!).
Or maybe you have this turned off and you're just studying. I need to put that in the title so everyone knows what this is really for.
For others, thinking about a second top 40 and all that is probably like that stupid story about the history of the penny.
Oh man this song sounds like Snake Eater, doesn't it? The one from Metal Gear Solid 3.
I'll link it in the dubleydoo.
Please Like, Subscribe and fuck yourself. It's sex with someone you love.
:D <3 :D
Anyway. I also wonder if that point in my life is when music stopped for me. Did I somehow close off to new music?
The National is a band that I feel so closed off to. I feel like they're so mediocre and so... safe? that it's offensive.
Or Coldplay? Same shit.
Though Spies is a DOPE song that everyone should listen to. I'll link to that one, it's the only tune that has stood the test of time for me.
I shouldn't say I'll link to things. Should just link to them and show that what I'm doing is a complete Youtube multimedia experience.
Ah I'm getting close!
The billboards that I see make me think. What do they mean? Someone's willing to spend money to put that sign up.
Movies are easy but when you see signs for weird expos, it's awesome.
Who knew that there were so many people into Underwater Basketweaving?
The UBE is going to be sick.
Thank you for watching.